Guide to the Betty Grover Eisner Papers SC0924
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audio materials, 1957-1972, undated; Series 6
  - Events and Talks
    - Meetings at La Mesa following the talks by Krishnamurti, 1972-03; 18.24; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 18)
    - Seminar on research on the mind at the Rand Corporation, 1963-10-07; 18.27; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 18)
  - unlabeled tape, 18.45; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 18)